Did you know that you and your computer speak different languages? It doesn’t speak Spanish,
당신과 컴퓨터는 서로 다른 언어를 사용한다는 걸 알고 있나요?
or Swedish, or Chinese; it speaks in ones and zeroes. You can’t communicate directly
컴퓨터는 스페인어 또는 스웨덴어 또는 중국어를 할 수 없습니다. 컴퓨터는 1과 0으로 말합니다
with your computer; that’s where your operating system comes in. The operating system is the
당신은 컴퓨터와 직접 대화할 수 없습니다. 컴퓨터 안에는 운영체제가 들어 있습니다.
program that lets you interact with your computer. Together, the operating system and
운영체제는 당신과 컴퓨터가 상호 작용할 수 있도록 해주는 프로그램입니다.
computer hardware form a complete system that determines what your computer can do. There
마찬가지로 운영체제와 컴퓨터 하드웨어는 컴퓨터가 수행할 수 있는 작업을 결정하는 완벽한 시스템을 구성합니다.
are many different operating systems. Two of the most common ones are Microsoft Windows
다양한 운영체제가 있습니다. 가장 일반적인 두가지가 있는데 Microsoft Windows 와 맥 OS X입니다.
and Mac OS X. Windows comes preloaded on most personal computers; Mac OS X runs on all new
Windows는 대부분의 개인용 컴퓨터에 미리 설치되어 있습니다. 맥 OS X는 모든 새로운 맥에서만 실행됩니다.
Macs. Operating Systems aren’t just for computers and laptops, though. Mobile devices
운영체제는 컴퓨터나 노트북 만 있는게 아닙니다.
run mobile operating systems like Apple iOS or Google Android. Operating systems for mobile
애플의 iOS 또는 구글 안드로이드와 같이 모바일 기기에서 실행되는 모바일 운영체제도 있습니다.
devices are designed for interactions with smaller touch-screens. Before downloading
모바일 기기를 위한 운영체제는 작은 터치스크린으로 상호작용하도록 설계되어 있습니다.
new software, or applications, to your computer or mobile device, you should check to see
당신의 컴퓨터나 모바일 기기에 새로운 소프트웨어나 응용프로그램을 다운로드 하기 전에
if the application is compatible with your operating system. Some applications work on
당신의 운영체제와 호환되는 응용프로그램인지 꼭 확인해야 합니다.
all operating systems, but others only work on certain ones. So, get to know your operating
일부의 프로그램은 모든 운영체제에서 실행되기도 하지만 대부분은 특정 운영체제에서만 작동합니다.
system to see how it works and what it can do.
따라서 운영체제가 무엇을 할 수 있고 어떻게 작동하는지 알아야 합니다.